24, Ezobi Street, Alapere-Ketu, Ketu, Lagos State, Nigeria

+2348102505757

Email: bellosmart2013@gmail.com Github: https://github.com/smabello

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/naseem-oyebola-40a0011a2

Smart Bello

I'm a web developer and graphic designer with over 2-years of experience working remote and onsite. Have a keen eye for design and appreciate the importance of a clean and beautiful user interface that engages the user and gives them the best experience.

SKILLS/TECHNOLOGIES

HTML, CSS, SCSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACTJS, REDUX, NODEJS, Restful API, Firebase, CorelDraw, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Third party libraries, Problem solving, Self-management, Teamwork

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Keystone Bank PLC 11/2021 - Present Lagos, Nigeria Keystone bank is a financial institution here in Nigeria. Achievements/Tasks

 Working on the customer application portal for mobile. Also converting some cross platform applications to native iOS Applications.

Graphic Designer

KudiGo Inc

08/21 - 10/2021 Ghana

KudiGo is a consumer retail software firm that offers data oriented solutions for the African Market. Achievements/Tasks

- Was involved in the development of the KudiGo StoreFront Application for the iOS platform using the SwiftUI framework.
- Designed the Onboarding workflow.
- Designed the verification mode screen where the user can choose to receive verification OTP via SMS or Whatsapp.
- Created the Terms and Condition page using HTMLView.
- Refactored the duplicated network service into a generic network manager thereby writing fewer code.

Designed the homepage/dashboard and its child views.

Brand Designer

Decagon Digital Institute

12/2020 - 07/2021

Lagos, Nigeria

Decagon is a Software Engineering institute that trains individuals to become world class developers. It also offers software engineering services to clients.

Achievements/Tasks

- Worked on a Food Delivery App, Foodly using Firebase as the database.
- Worked on a Fintech Application, Closed Circuit.
- Refactored the duplicated network service into a generic network manager thereby writing fewer code.
- Implemented the authentication feature of the App which includes the password recovery feature.
- Designed the Cart page whereby users can add items to the cart, remove items and apply promo codes to get discounts and tax deductions as well.
- Built an iOS App that displays news using the SwiftUI framework. iOS Developer Intern Serve

Consulting.

02/2020-06/2020

Lagos, Nigeria

Serve Consulting is a leading SAP service provider in Nigeria. Clannit is a community app that connects like-minded people. It provides a marketplace for people to buy and sell their goods, find common interests, and access control the community. Clannit is also a residential community that offers alarm systems, and we have a collection of smart devices to make your home easier to manage.

Achievements/Tasks

 Was part of the core development team and I specifically worked on the alarm feature. When the alarm button is pressed, everyone in the clan receives a notification with sound and vibration and there are different alarms for different situations.

PROJECTS

- Clannit https://apps.apple.com/ng/app/clannit/id1450717092
- Javat365 https://apps.apple.com/ng/app/javat-365/id1525814384
- TrelloAppClone https://github.com/OBaller/TrelloAppCloneSwiftUI
- CaloryMeter https://github.com/OBaller/CaloryMeter
- Foodly https://github.com/OBaller/FoodlyNas
- Football Fixtures App https://github.com/OBaller/Football_Fixtures
- ExchangeRateCalculator https://github.com/OBaller/XchangeCalculator.git
- SwiftUINews App https://github.com/OBaller/SwiftUI-News

- CoffeeApp https://github.com/OBaller/SwiftUI-CoffeeApp
- BucketList https://github.com/OBaller/BucketList.git
- BiometricAuthentication https://github.com/OBaller/BiometricAuthentication.git
- PhotoGallery- https://github.com/OBaller/UnsplashPixels
- CoreDataProject- https://github.com/OBaller/CoreDataProject
- StripePayment https://github.com/OBaller/PaymentGateway

EDUCATION

Obafemi Awolowo University— BSc.

May 2015 - August 2020

Bachelor of Science in Industrial Chemistry from Obafemi Awolowo University, Ile-Ife, Osun State, Nigeria.

CERTIFICATIONS

Scrum Fundamentals Certified(SFC)

SCRUMstudy -Accreditation body for Scrum and Agile.

Link:https://www.scrumstudy.com/certification/verify?type=SFC&number=832069

Credential ID: 832069

Jobberman Soft-Skills Certificate

Link: http://www.coursera.org/verify/E7RBGV3Q7CNZ